xp-vista.com 2008-06-16

# Privacy Policy For Windows XP/Vista

##  Privacy Policy 

Windows-XP-Vista.com and XP-Vista.com Privacy Policy

Information Collection and Use

XP-Vista.com is the sole owner of the information collected on its web properties, including Windows-XP-Vista.com, XP-Vista.com collects information from its users at several different points on our Web sites.

Information Use

Subject to the legal exceptions listed in the Privacy Policy, XP-Vista.com will not disclose to third parties the email addresses uploaded to our Web sites by our users for the purpose of using XP-Vista.com products or services.

Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. For the session cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions.

Log Files

Like most Web sites, our servers use log files to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

Service Announcements

On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. These communications are not promotional in nature.

Spam

XP-Vista.com has a zero tolerance policy for abuse.

Sharing

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. For example, XP-Vista.com may disclose personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or third parties in response to criminal or civil subpoenas.
